<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.lafd.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alerts Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.lafd.org/</link>
    <description>Alerts Feeds -- Los Angeles Fire Department</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml"/>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 09:16:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 09:16:00 -0800</pubDate>

    <item>
  <title><a href="/alert/evacuation-order-02042024" hreflang="en">EVACUATION ORDER 02/04/2024</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/evacuation-order-02042024" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>EVACUATION ORDER; 09:15AM; MAP: &lt;a href="https://lafd.maps.arcgis.com/apps/Media/index.html?appid=ba8cfed4b4a04d49b7489eb8300727a8" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://lafd.maps.arcgis.com/apps/Media/index.html?appid=ba8cfed4b4a04d49b7489eb8300727a8&lt;/a&gt;; #ShadowHills; EVACUATE NOW due to the high risk of debris flow triggered by heavy rain from the storm impacting the area today through Tuesday. The EVACUATION ORDER is for the La Tuna Canyon Road area, with borders of Horse Haven Street to the North, Martindale Avenue to the East, Penrose Street to the South, Ledge Avenue to the West. Evacuation Centers for people and household pets have opened at Sunland Senior Citizen Center (8640 Fenwick St, Sunland, CA 91040) and Lake View Terrace Recreation Center (11075 Foothill Blvd, Lake View Terrace, CA 91342). Large animals can be evacuated to Hansen Dam Horse Park (11127 Orcas Ave. Lake View Terrace, CA 91342) and the LA Equestrian Center (480 Riverside Dr, Burbank, CA 91506). Check lafd.org/alerts for updates on this evacuation order. Debris flows can bring water, mud, boulders, and other debris that can cover cars and houses.  Pack all people and pets into your vehicle and leave the area immediately. More information, including a map, can be found at www.lafd.org/news

EVACUEN AHORA debido al flujo de escombros de alto riesgo provocado por las fuertes lluvias de la tormenta que impactaran el área desde hoy hasta el martes. La ORDEN DE EVACUACIÓN es para el área La Tuna Canyon Road, con límites de Horse Haven St. al norte, Martindale Ave. al este, Penrose St al sur, Ledge Ave al oeste. Se han abierto refugios para personas y mascotas domésticas en Sunland Senior Citizen Center (8640 Fenwick St, Sunland, CA 91040) y Lake View Terrace Recreation Center (11075 Foothill Blvd, Lake View Terrace, CA 91342). Los animales grandes pueden ser evacuados al Hansen Dam Horse Park (11127 Orcas Ave. Lake View Terrace, CA 91342) y al LA Equestrian Center (480 Riverside Dr, Burbank, CA 91506). Visite lafd.org/alerts para obtener actualizaciones sobre esta orden de evacuación.
Los flujos de escombros pueden traer agua, lodo, rocas y otros escombros que pueden cubrir automóviles y casas. Empaque a todas las personas y mascotas en su vehículo y abandone el área inmediatamente. Puede encontrar más información, incluido un mapa, en www.lafd.org/news; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>EVACUATION ORDER</category>
                            <category>#ShadowHills</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/evacuation-order-02042024" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 09:16</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire 02/03/2024 INC#1609</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#1609; 11:51PM; 7255 N Clybourn Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/ayaoto8T2gajhhQu9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/ayaoto8T2gajhhQu9&lt;/a&gt;; #SunValley; It took 78 firefighters 61 minutes operating in defensive mode to extinguish the blaze consuming the 80' x 120' one-story commercial structure. One man from the scene was transported to a local hospital with a medical complaint (not directly related to smoke or fire). LAFD Heavy Equipment and RS3 (remote firefighting vehicle) will be performing an extended operation to ensure all the hot spots and smoldering debris are uncovered for extinguishment. No firefighter injuries. Cause under investigation.; FS 89; Batt 14; Valley Bureau; Council District 2; AR1  BC11  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E102  E227  E239  E260  E27  E278  E289  E298  E60  E75  E77  E86  E87  E89  EA1  EM14  EM5  HE1  HR3  PI3  RA77  RA86  RA889  RA89  RS3  SO1  SQ87  T27  T39  T60  T78  T89  T98  UR27  UR88; CH8; 12  13  15; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#SunValley</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 00:31</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 02/03/2024</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; 10:50PM; 7255 N Clybourn Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/7WpyzXuBMEygM3dw5" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/7WpyzXuBMEygM3dw5&lt;/a&gt;; #SunValley; One-story commercial building with heavy fire through the roof. Defensive mode.; FS 89; Batt 14; Valley Bureau; Council District 2; BC11  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E102  E227  E239  E260  E27  E289  E298  E60  E77  E86  E87  E89  EM14  HR3  RA889  RA89  SQ87  T27  T39  T60  T89  T98  UR27  UR88; CH9; 12  13; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#SunValley</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 23:00</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 02/03/2024 INC#1609</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; INC#1609; 10:50PM; 7255 N Clybourn Av; #SunValley; One-story commercial building with heavy fire through the roof. Defensive mode.; FS 89; Batt 14; Valley Bureau; Council District 2; BC11  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E102  E227  E239  E260  E27  E289  E298  E60  E77  E86  E87  E89  EM14  HR3  RA889  RA89  SQ87  T27  T39  T60  T89  T98  UR27  UR88; CH9; 12  13; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#SunValley</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 22:59</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/evacuation-warning-02042024" hreflang="en">EVACUATION WARNING 02/04/2024</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/evacuation-warning-02042024" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>EVACUATION WARNING; 10:00PM; MAP: &lt;a href="https://www.lafd.org/news/strong-february-rain-storm-hits-los-angeles-area" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.lafd.org/news/strong-february-rain-storm-hits-los-angeles-area&lt;/a&gt;; #ShadowHills; LAFD: A strong storm coming Sunday-Tuesday may trigger a life-threatening debris flow. EVACUATION WARNING: La Tuna Canyon Road starting at Martindale to the east, Primrose to the south, Ledge to the west, Horse Haven to the north should prepare to evacuate. This will likely be upgraded to an evacuation order at 8am Sunday. Check lafd.org/alerts for updates.

LAFD: Una fuerte tormenta que comience el domingo hasta martes puede provocar flujos de escombros que pongan en peligro la vida. ADVERTENCIA DE EVACUACIÓN: La Tuna Canyon Rd. comenzando en Martindale al este, Primrose al sur, Ledge al oeste y Horse Haven al norte deben prepararse para evacuar. Es probable que esto se actualice a una orden de evacuación a las 8 a.m. del domingo. Consulte lafd.org/alerts para obtener actualizaciones.; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>EVACUATION WARNING</category>
                            <category>#ShadowHills</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/evacuation-warning-02042024" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 22:01</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-confined-space-rescue-02032024-inc1224" hreflang="en">Update Confined Space Rescue 02/03/2024 INC#1224</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-confined-space-rescue-02032024-inc1224" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Confined Space Rescue; INC#1224; 09:30PM; EB 118 Fwy x Laurel Canyon Blvd; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/eaWHf1fGHVqxpoR37" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/eaWHf1fGHVqxpoR37&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; Rescuers thoroughly searched the tunnels/drains/channels and did not locate an injured female, as reported. One adult male was located, but did not wish to receive LAFD assistance in any way. Crews will be picking up the equipment and clearing the scene shortly.; FS 75; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; BC12  BC14  E18  E27  E275  E288  E289  E298  E75  E87  E88  E89  EM15  HR3  PI3  RA70  RA75  RA96  SO1  SQ87  T75  T88  T89  T98  UR88  UR89; CH8; 12  13; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Confined Space Rescue</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-confined-space-rescue-02032024-inc1224" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 21:45</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/confined-space-rescue-02032024-inc1224" hreflang="en">Confined Space Rescue 02/03/2024 INC#1224</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/confined-space-rescue-02032024-inc1224" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Confined Space Rescue; INC#1224; 06:14PM; EB 118 Fwy x Laurel Canyon Blvd; #Pacoima; One adult female is trapped in a storm drain with unknown injuries. Urban Search and Rescue teams are responding to make entry into the confined space.; FS 75; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; BC12  BC14  E18  E27  E275  E288  E289  E75  E87  E88  EM15  HR3  RA70  RA75  RA96  SO1  SQ87  T75  T88  T89  UR88  UR89; CH8; 12  13; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Confined Space Rescue</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/confined-space-rescue-02032024-inc1224" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 19:18</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-02032024-inc0930" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Structure Fire 02/03/2024 INC#0930</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-02032024-inc0930" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Structure Fire; INC#0930; 02:43PM; 7230 N Medical Center Dr; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/fiAWHCXYzmFZyx2z9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/fiAWHCXYzmFZyx2z9&lt;/a&gt;; #WestHills; Firefighters found a small fire on the fourth floor of a medical center building, held in check by a fire sprinkler. Forty-six firefighters responded to the modern sealed six-story building and took 26 minutes to access and extinguish the flames, which were well-contained by the sprinklers. Firefighters will be on scene for an extended operation to clear the building of water and smoke. resulting from the fire and sprinklers. No reported injuries. Cause under investigation.; FS 106; Batt 17; Valley Bureau; Council District 12; BC10  BC15  BC17  CM40  CM42  E104  E106  E273  E296  E305  E72  E84  EM17  RA106  RA72  RA84  SO1  T105  T73  T96; CH8; 17; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#WestHills</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-02032024-inc0930" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 15:40</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024-inc0930" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 02/03/2024 INC#0930</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024-inc0930" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; INC#0930; 02:43PM; 7230 N Medical Center Dr; #WestHills; Six-story medical center building with fire showing from the fourth floor. Reports of fire sprinkler activations on that floor. Offensive mode.; FS 106; Batt 17; Valley Bureau; Council District 12; BC15  BC17  CM40  CM42  E106  E296  E305  E72  E84  RA106  RA72  SO1  T105  T96; CH9; 17; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#WestHills</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02032024-inc0930" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 15:01</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-02032024-inc0596" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Structure Fire 02/03/2024 INC#0596</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-02032024-inc0596" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Structure Fire; INC#0596; 11:23AM; 4418 N Homer St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/xUY9GqhQjsH27xR18" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/xUY9GqhQjsH27xR18&lt;/a&gt;; #MontecitoHeights; Firefighters responded to a one-story home with heavy fire in the attic, and some extension into the living space below. Crews advanced hose lines through crowded rooms with excessive storage to gain access to the fire from below. Additional firefighters ascended ladders to the roof to cut holes for ventilation, and made great progress to extinguish flames with hose lines from above (spraying hose lines down through the holes they made). Ultimately, it took 32 firefighters 20 minutes to eliminate the fire. One occupant escaped in good health. Paramedics provided a medical evaluation as a precaution, but the occupant chose not to accept ambulance transport to the hospital. No further injuries. Cause under investigation.; FS 1; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; BC1  BC2  E1  E12  E201  E212  E44  RA1  RA12  RA801  SC1  SO1  SQ21  T1  T12; CH7; 12; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#MontecitoHeights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-02032024-inc0596" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Saturday, February 3, 2024 - 11:40</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
