<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.lafd.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alerts Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.lafd.org/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml"/>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:56:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Sunday, October 23, 2022 - 15:47</pubDate>

    <item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-fire-10232022-inc0915" hreflang="en">Knockdown -  Fire 10/23/2022 INC#0915</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-fire-10232022-inc0915" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Knockdown -  Fire; INC#0915; 03:19PM; 14608 W Titus St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3TKiDHy" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3TKiDHy&lt;/a&gt;; #PanoramaCity; It took 54 LAFD Firefighters just 43 minutes to access and confine flames to a large mulch pile (90' long x 45' wide x 20' high), as well as fully extinguish three parked (and empty) 'open top' mulch trailers that were ablaze on LAFD arrival. Firefighters prevented the half-dozen other vehicles and one commercial building from direct harm by flames. No injury. LAFD personnel will remain at scene this evening using tractors and other heavy equipment to assist in the full extinguishment of the smoldering debris. #LATraffic: Full closure of Titus Street between Van Nuys Boulevard and Cedros Avenue will continue until LAFD operations are complete, unknown duration. Fire cause under active investigation.; FS 81; Batt 10; Valley Bureau; Council District 6; BC10  BC17  CM40  CM42  E100  E239  E288  E289  E290  E39  E81  E88  EM14  HE1  RA39  RA81  RA881  T39  T88  T89  T90; CH9; 17; - Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Fire</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#PanoramaCity</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-fire-10232022-inc0915" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Sunday, October 23, 2022 - 15:47</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/fire-10232022-inc0915" hreflang="en">Fire 10/23/2022 INC#0915</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/fire-10232022-inc0915" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Fire; INC#0915; 02:36PM; 14608 W Titus St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3TKiDHy" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3TKiDHy&lt;/a&gt;; #PanoramaCity; PRELIM: Fire involving a large mulch pile has extended to three parked tractor-trailer rigs (unknown cargo), and currently threatening as many as six other vehicles and one commercial building in a non-residential neighborhood. #LATraffic: Full closure of Titus Street between Van Nuys Boulevard and Cedros Avenue until LAFD operations are complete, unknown duration.; FS 81; Batt 10; Valley Bureau; Council District 6; BC10  BC17  CM40  CM42  E100  E239  E288  E289  E290  E39  E81  E88  EM14  RA39  RA81  RA881  T39  T88  T89  T90; CH9; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Fire</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#PanoramaCity</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/fire-10232022-inc0915" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Sunday, October 23, 2022 - 14:57</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/hiker-rescue-10232022-inc0658" hreflang="en">Hiker Rescue 10/23/2022 INC#0658</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/hiker-rescue-10232022-inc0658" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Hiker Rescue; INC#0658; 11:24AM; Bell Canyon Park; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3F8CKuM" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3F8CKuM&lt;/a&gt;; #WestHills; PRELIM: LAFD ground and air response to an adult male hiker injured in a ground-level fall on or near the El Escorpion Trail. An LAFD helicopter has lowered a flight medic and will work with LAFD ground crews to treat and prepare the patient for in-flight care during direct LAFD helicopter transport to a regional trauma center.; FS 105; Batt 17; Valley Bureau; Council District 12; BC17  E105  E290  E305  E73  H1  H3  HA1  HA3  RA72  RH114  T105  T90; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Hiker Rescue</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#WestHills</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/hiker-rescue-10232022-inc0658" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Sunday, October 23, 2022 - 12:01</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-fatality-traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">Update Fatality Traffic Collision with Entrapment 10/22/2022 INC#1156</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-fatality-traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Fatality Traffic Collision with Entrapment; INC#1156; 07:15PM; 11001 N Reseda Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3MXAI2H" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3MXAI2H&lt;/a&gt;; #PorterRanch; Three vehicle collision with a total of 10 patients (7 Adults / 3 Minors), including one 17 year-old male badly trapped in the wreckage. Despite the efforts of LAFD responders, that teenager sadly proved beyond medical help and he was determined deceased at the scene. No other entrapment. Nine patients have been transported to regional trauma centers (6 patients in Critical Condition and 3 in Fair Condition). No further details. #LATraffic: Full closure of Reseda Blvd in both directions between San Fernando Mission Boulevard and Chatsworth Street will remain in effect until LAPD on-site investigation and scene clean-up are complete, unknown duration. Motorists, expect congestion and delay, avoid the immediate area and consider an alternate route. Detours are readily available. Media Inquiries: LAPD Valley Traffic Division (Incident #2927) and Coroner.; FS 70; Batt 15; Valley Bureau; Council District 12; BC12  BC15  CM40  CM42  E103  E104  E18  E273  E275  E28  E287  E70  E8  EM14  EM15  EM17  HR3  RA104  RA18  RA7  RA70  RA72  RA75  RA87  RA881  RA898  RA96  T73  T75  T87  UR88; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Fatality Traffic Collision with Entrapment</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#PorterRanch</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-fatality-traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Saturday, October 22, 2022 - 19:18</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">Update Traffic Collision with Entrapment 10/22/2022 INC#1156</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Traffic Collision with Entrapment; INC#1156; 05:52PM; 11001 N Reseda Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3MXAI2H" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3MXAI2H&lt;/a&gt;; #PorterRanch; Now described as a three vehicle collision with a total of *eight* patients, one of whom is trapped. Awaiting details on age/gender/condition/affiliation/circumstances. #LATraffic: Full closure of Reseda Blvd in both directions between San Fernando Mission Boulevard and Chatsworth Street until LAFD operations are complete, unknown duration. Motorists, expect congestion and delay, avoid the immediate area and consider an alternate route. Detours are readily available. ; FS 70; Batt 15; Valley Bureau; Council District 12; BC12  BC15  CM40  CM42  E103  E104  E18  E273  E275  E28  E287  E70  E8  EM14  EM15  EM17  HR3  RA104  RA18  RA70  RA75  RA87  T73  T75  T87  UR88; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Traffic Collision with Entrapment</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#PorterRanch</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Saturday, October 22, 2022 - 17:52</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">Traffic Collision with Entrapment 10/22/2022 INC#1156</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Traffic Collision with Entrapment; INC#1156; 05:35PM; 11001 N Reseda Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3MXAI2H" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3MXAI2H&lt;/a&gt;; #PorterRanch; PRELIM: Three vehicle collision with entrapment. Five critically injured patients.; FS 70; Batt 15; Valley Bureau; Council District 12; BC15  E103  E275  E70  E8  EM15  HR3  RA18  RA70  RA87  T75  UR88; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Traffic Collision with Entrapment</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#PorterRanch</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/traffic-collision-entrapment-10222022-inc1156" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Saturday, October 22, 2022 - 17:44</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/fatality-traffic-collision-10222022-inc0051" hreflang="en">Fatality Traffic Collision 10/22/2022 INC#0051</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/fatality-traffic-collision-10222022-inc0051" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Fatality Traffic Collision; INC#0051; 12:47AM; WB 210 Fwy east of Roxford St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3cnwNy1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3cnwNy1&lt;/a&gt;; #Sylmar; Solo vehicle vs. Caltrans forklift at highway work zone. 3 adult male civilian patients total. One is deceased and remains trapped in the vehicle. The others were both 30 year-old males, one of whom self-extricated prior to LAFD arrival, the other who was briefly trapped in the vehicle before being freed by firefighters. Both have been taken by LAFD ambulance to an area hospital with non-life threatening injuries. No Caltrans / construction workers were injured. Media Inquiries: CHP Newhall (Log #160) and Coroner.; FS 91; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; BC12  E18  E275  E75  E91  EM14  HR3  RA75  RA91  T75; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Fatality Traffic Collision</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#Sylmar</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/fatality-traffic-collision-10222022-inc0051" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Saturday, October 22, 2022 - 01:21</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/traffic-collision-10212022-inc1231" hreflang="en">Traffic Collision 10/21/2022 INC#1231</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/traffic-collision-10212022-inc1231" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Traffic Collision; INC#1231; 04:02PM; 12100 W Ventura Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3VZWPK2" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3VZWPK2&lt;/a&gt;; #StudioCity; PRELIM: Traffic collision with one vehicle into business, possibly injuring four persons within (1 adult, 3 children). No entrapment. Structural damage will require Dept of Building &amp; Safety evaluation. No further details. Media Inquiries: LAPD Valley Traffic Division  (Incident #2873); FS 78; Batt 14; Valley Bureau; Council District 4; BC14  E278  EM14  RA827  RA86  RA97  T78; CH8; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Traffic Collision</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#StudioCity</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/traffic-collision-10212022-inc1231" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Friday, October 21, 2022 - 16:18</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-hazardous-materials-investigation-10212022-inc1082" hreflang="en">Update Hazardous Materials Investigation 10/21/2022 INC#1082</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-hazardous-materials-investigation-10212022-inc1082" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Hazardous Materials Investigation; INC#1082; 03:20PM; 911 E 61st St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3SiFPvf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3SiFPvf&lt;/a&gt;; #Florence; LAFD Hazardous Materials experts have entered the one-story building in which the demolition work was taking place *above* an in-ground pit. The cutting work being performed by the demolition crew above that indoor pit, appears to have created a spark that displaced the lid of an in-ground tank, containing a very limited amount of Phosphine gas, that quickly discharged from the tank and dissipated. There was no indication of fire, smoke or fumes on LAFD arrival, and no injury or acute illness experienced by the three demolition workers, who safely self-evacuated the *building* unharmed and without any apparent contamination. No escalating or off-site hazard has been identified, and there is no evacuation. Pursuant to protocol, LAFD personnel checked in on the occupants of nearby buildings to confirm them OK, and have asked them to briefly "shelter in place" until LAFD operations area complete. The situation is stable, and the scene will soon be turned over to County Health officials for requisite documentation and to coordinate any necessary clean up.; FS 33; Batt 13; South Bureau; Council District 9; BC13  E21  E221  E294  E33  EM13  JT1  JT6  RA33  RA57  SQ21  T21  T94; CH7; 13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Hazardous Materials Investigation</category>
          <category>South</category>
          <category>#Florence</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-hazardous-materials-investigation-10212022-inc1082" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Friday, October 21, 2022 - 15:20</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/hazardous-materials-investigation-10212022-inc1082" hreflang="en">Hazardous Materials Investigation 10/21/2022 INC#1082</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/hazardous-materials-investigation-10212022-inc1082" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Hazardous Materials Investigation; INC#1082; 02:10PM; 911 E 61st St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3SiFPvf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3SiFPvf&lt;/a&gt;; #Florence; PRELIM: LAFD summoned to a subterranean (utility/storage?) vault, where three workers performing demolition appear to have caused some manner of (unknown) product release that led to a smoke / fume discharge, but no fire on LAFD arrival. The three workers were able to safely evacuate the (unknown size or depth) in-ground chamber unharmed and without any apparent contamination. No other injuries. No fire, smoke or fumes on LAFD arrival. Though the immediate area has been isolated to support LAFD operations, no escalating or off-site hazard has been identified, and there is no evacuation. Pursuant to protocol, LAFD Hazardous Materials experts will soon enter the enclosed site to perform a rapid environmental assessment, and better determine the nature of the incident. ; FS 33; Batt 13; South Bureau; Council District 9; BC13  E21  E221  E294  E33  EM13  JT1  JT6  RA33  RA57  SQ21  T21  T94; CH7; 13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Hazardous Materials Investigation</category>
          <category>South</category>
          <category>#Florence</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/hazardous-materials-investigation-10212022-inc1082" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Friday, October 21, 2022 - 14:40</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
