<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.lafd.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alerts Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.lafd.org/</link>
    <description>Alerts Feeds -- Los Angeles Fire Department</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml"/>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 10:02:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>

    <item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Structure Fire 08/22/2023 INC#0145</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Structure Fire; INC#0145; 05:53AM; 9800 N San Fernando Rd; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/45igQQd" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/45igQQd&lt;/a&gt;; Pacoima; KNOCKDOWN: Over 100 firefighters extinguished the fire in two hours and 20 minutes with no injuries reported.  A portion of the LAFD resources will remain on scene through the morning for the extensive overhaul operation utilizing heavy equipment. No further details.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; BC12  BC14  BC15  CM40  CM42  E227  E239  E24  E273  E275  E287  E289  E290  E298  E7  E75  E77  E81  E87  E89  E98  EM14  EM15  HE1  HR3  RA77  RA889  RA898  RA98  RS3  SO1  SQ87  T27  T39  T73  T75  T87  T89  T90  T98  UR88  UR89; CH8; 17  18; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 05:54</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-3" hreflang="en">Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation 08/22/2023 INC#1955</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-3" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation; INC#1955; 05:27AM; 1720 E Chavez Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3E70ttO" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3E70ttO&lt;/a&gt;; Boyle Heights; A press conference will be held at 7:00AM at 1820 Cesar Chavez Ave. Representatives from White Memorial and LAFD will be speaking. 17 critical patients have been transported with more patients being prepared for transport.  The movement of the non-critical patients to other facilities within White Memorial is continuing. Those with family members at the Specialty Care Center (the only building affected) can contact the main White Memorial number for information 323-268-5000.; FS 2; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 14; BC1  BC10  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM21  CM22  E1  E10  E11  E12  E14  E15  E16  E17  E2  E201  E202  E203  E209  E210  E220  E235  E25  E260  E3  E4  E44  E47  E9  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  PI3  PI4  RA1  RA11  RA12  RA15  RA2  RA20  RA209  RA21  RA246  RA25  RA266  RA3  RA35  RA4  RA46  RA47  RA57  RA76  RA79  RA801  RA803  RA809  RA810  RA82  RA86  RA9  RA900  SO1  T1  T10  T2  T20  T3  T35  T60  T9; CH7; 12; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>Boyle Heights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-3" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 05:28</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145-0" hreflang="en">Update Structure Fire 08/22/2023 INC#0145</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145-0" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Structure Fire; INC#0145; 03:33AM; 9800 N San Fernando Rd; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/45igQQd" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/45igQQd&lt;/a&gt;; Pacoima; Firefighters have extinguished the bulk of the auto fires and are shutting down the ladder pipe operations to transition into an offensive attack with handlines because the remaining fire is deep seated in stacks of tires. No injuries reported. No additional resources anticipated. ; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; BC12  BC14  BC15  CM40  CM42  E227  E239  E24  E273  E275  E287  E289  E290  E298  E7  E75  E77  E81  E87  E89  E98  EM14  EM15  HE1  HR3  RA77  RA889  RA898  RA98  RS3  SO1  SQ87  T27  T39  T73  T75  T87  T89  T90  T98  UR88  UR89; CH9; 17  18; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145-0" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 04:33</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">Update Structure Fire 08/22/2023 INC#0145</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Structure Fire; INC#0145; 04:07AM; 12400 W Branford St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ONOuq5" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ONOuq5&lt;/a&gt;; Pacoima; This incident is now at the Greater Alarm status. The fire location is updated to an auto yard (fenced) with multiple autos fully involved (stacked). There have been challenges with water supply at hydrants and firefighters are working to establish alternate supplies. This is a defensive operation with ladder pipe and large diameter hand lines in place. There are no injuries reported. ; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 6; BC12  BC14  BC15  CM40  CM42  E227  E275  E287  E289  E290  E298  E7  E75  E77  E81  E89  E98  EM14  EM15  HR3  RA77  RA889  RA898  RA98  SO1  SQ87  T27  T75  T87  T89  T90  T98  UR88  UR89; CH9; 17  18; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 04:08</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-2" hreflang="en">Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation 08/22/2023 INC#1955</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-2" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation; INC#1955; 03:50AM; 1720 E Chavez Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3E70ttO" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3E70ttO&lt;/a&gt;; Boyle Heights; The incident is stabilizing with an updated count for patients requiring LAFD transport of 21. The transportation is underway.  The bulk of the 241 patients will be moved to the South Tower at White Memorial as only the Specialty Care Center was affected by the power outage. LAFD is able to release some of the rescue ambulances back to their respective districts. Any questions regarding the power outage are referred to White Memorial. Media staging remains at Michigan Ave x N Boyle Ave.; FS 2; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 14; BC1  BC10  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM21  CM22  E1  E10  E11  E12  E14  E15  E16  E17  E2  E201  E202  E203  E209  E210  E220  E235  E25  E260  E3  E4  E44  E47  E9  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  PI3  PI4  RA1  RA11  RA12  RA15  RA2  RA20  RA209  RA21  RA25  RA3  RA35  RA4  RA46  RA47  RA801  RA803  RA809  RA810  RA9  RA900  SO1  T1  T10  T2  T20  T3  T35  T60  T9; CH7; 12; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>Boyle Heights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-2" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 03:52</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 08/22/2023 INC#0145</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; INC#0145; 03:33AM; 12400 W Branford St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ONOuq5" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ONOuq5&lt;/a&gt;; Pacoima; One story (approx 75'x75') commercial building (auto body/tire shop) with fire showing upon arrival. Two additional task forces were requested. A defensive operation was initiated and located multiple autos fully involved inside the structure.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 6; BC12  BC14  BC15  CM40  CM42  E227  E275  E289  E290  E298  E7  E75  E77  E81  E89  E98  EM15  HR3  RA889  RA898  RA98  SO1  T27  T75  T89  T90  T98  UR88  UR89; CH9; 17  18; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-08222023-inc0145" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 03:50</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-1" hreflang="en">Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation 08/22/2023 INC#1955</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-1" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation; INC#1955; 02:12AM; 1720 E Chavez Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3E70ttO" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3E70ttO&lt;/a&gt;; Boyle Heights; A total of 241 patients are affected by the power outage in one building (Specialty Care Center) at White Memorial Hospital campus. A total of 30 patients deemed critical requiring LAFD ambulance transportation to a new hospital. Firefighters are bringing them down to the ground floor, assisting ventilations as required, for transport. The remaining 211 patients are non-critical and will be moved to a different building on campus (South Tower). LAFD will assist White Memorial staff, as needed, in the move. Any questions regarding the outage are referred to White Memorial. LAFD Media staging remains at Michigan Av x N Boyle Ave.; FS 2; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 14; BC1  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM21  CM22  E1  E10  E11  E14  E15  E16  E17  E2  E201  E202  E203  E209  E210  E220  E235  E25  E3  E4  E44  E47  E9  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  PI3  PI4  RA1  RA11  RA12  RA15  RA2  RA20  RA209  RA21  RA25  RA3  RA35  RA4  RA46  RA47  RA801  RA803  RA809  RA810  RA9  RA900  SO1  T1  T10  T2  T20  T3  T35  T9; CH7; 12; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>Boyle Heights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-1" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 02:18</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955" hreflang="en">Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation 08/22/2023 INC#1955</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation; INC#1955; 01:48AM; 1720 E Chavez Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3E70ttO" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3E70ttO&lt;/a&gt;; Boyle Heights; The power outage is only affecting one building (Specialty Care Center) on the White Memorial campus. An estimated 30 patients are identified as critical, requiring transport to one of the designated hospitals. This includes some pediatric and OB/GYN patients. The bulk of the patients in the facility are non critical and can be moved to another building on the campus. Media staging is Michigan Ave x N Boyle Ave  IMPORTANT NOTE: Please ensure all roads are kept CLEAR for ambulance traffic.; FS 2; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 14; BC1  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM21  CM22  E1  E10  E11  E14  E15  E16  E17  E2  E201  E202  E203  E209  E210  E220  E235  E25  E3  E4  E44  E47  E9  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  PI3  PI4  RA1  RA11  RA12  RA15  RA2  RA20  RA209  RA21  RA25  RA3  RA35  RA4  RA46  RA47  RA801  RA803  RA809  RA810  RA9  RA900  SO1  T1  T10  T2  T20  T3  T35  T9; CH7; 12; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>Boyle Heights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 01:54</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-0" hreflang="en">Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation 08/22/2023 INC#1955</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-0" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation; INC#1955; 12:54AM; 1720 E Chavez Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3E70ttO" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3E70ttO&lt;/a&gt;; Boyle Heights; LAFD is working with White Memorial staff and identifying prioritization of patients requiring transport to a new hospital with those on ventilators (assisted breathing) receiving top priority.  Due to the power outage, firefighters must physically transport patients down from upper floors to awaiting ambulances. Initial focus on 11 identified patients. LAFD PIO CII Cody Weireter is enroute to assist with media availability, however questions regarding their standard operating procedures in the case of (what is called an) internal disaster are referred to White Memorial. ; FS 2; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 14; BC1  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM22  E1  E2  E201  E202  E209  E220  E3  E4  E9  EM1  EM11  EM13  RA1  RA11  RA12  RA15  RA2  RA20  RA209  RA21  RA25  RA3  RA35  RA4  RA46  RA47  RA801  RA803  RA809  RA810  RA9  RA900  T1  T2  T20  T9; CH7; 12; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>Boyle Heights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955-0" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 00:54</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955" hreflang="en">Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation 08/22/2023 INC#1955</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation; INC#1955; 11:45PM; 1720 E Chavez Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3E70ttO" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3E70ttO&lt;/a&gt;; Boyle Heights; Power outage at White Memorial hospital requiring evacuation of patients on ventilators (assisted breathing). Exact number of patients needed evacuation is being determined. LAFD will assist in both caring for patients and transporting them to designated hospitals.  Any questions regarding the power outage and their standard operation in such scenario are referred to White Memorial.; FS 2; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 14; BC1  BC11  CM20  CM22  E2  E201  E202  E4  EM1  EM11  EM13  RA1  RA2  RA25  RA4  RA801  RA803  RA809  RA810  RA9  RA900  T1  T2  T9; CH7; 12; Margaret Stewart</description>
  <category>Automatic Alarm - Medical Evacuation</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>Boyle Heights</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/automatic-alarm-medical-evacuation-08222023-inc1955" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 - 00:30</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
