<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.lafd.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alerts Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.lafd.org/</link>
    <description>Alerts Feeds -- Los Angeles Fire Department</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml"/>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 22:31:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>

    <item>
  <title><a href="/alert/major-emergency-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">Major Emergency Structure Fire 07/12/2023 INC#1353</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/major-emergency-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Major Emergency Structure Fire; INC#1353; 07:03PM; 7764 W Hollywood Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m&lt;/a&gt;; #Hollywood; 126 LAFD Firefighters - joined by neighboring Los Angeles County Firefighters in Automatic Aid, engaged in a fierce 102 minute firefight (5:21 PM to 7:03 PM) to access, confine and extinguish this Major Emergency blaze. The fire was initially reported as a pair of vehicles burning in a apartment carport, which extended to involve two of three identical side-by-side apartment buildings, including the thirty-two unit, 18,900 square foot two-story centrally located apartment building of fire origin, where flames that had already extended to the large common attic on LAFD arrival, caused severe damage to that attic and sixteen apartment units on the second floor, including structural compromise and partial collapse. Flames from that building extended to stubbornly involve the attic of the identical adjoining apartment buildings to the *east*, which sustained severe attic damage. An additional three story apartment building *further east* at the southwest corner of Hollywood Boulevard and Genesee Avenue, sustained only smoke damage. The woman with mobility challenges who had been trapped by smoke and flames on the second floor of the apartment building of fire origin, was rescued by first arriving LAFD Firefighters. She was initially described as being in fair condition after sustaining smoke exposure, and is now being treated at an area hospital. One LAFD Firefighter sustained a hand laceration during fire attack. After being treated at scene, he returned to the firefight. No other injuries have been reported. The cause of the fire is under active investigation. MEDIA: LAFD Public Information Officer Captain Erik Scott is en route, ETA 8:15 PM.; FS 41; Batt 5; West Bureau; Council District 13; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC18  BC5  CE83  CM20  CM22  CM52  E11  E203  E220  E226  E227  E229  E235  E261  E27  E278  E29  E3  E41  E61  E88  E97  EA1  EM11  EM14  EM9  HR3  PH1  RA41  RA52  RA76  RA803  RA82  RA97  SQ21  T20  T26  T27  T29  T3  T35  T61  T78  UR3  UR88  + 
 LACoFD  BC1  E7  LF8; CH9; 12  13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Major Emergency Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>West</category>
                            <category>#Hollywood</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/major-emergency-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 19:47</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">Update Major Emergency Structure Fire 07/12/2023 INC#1353</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Major Emergency Structure Fire; INC#1353; 06:30PM; 7764 W Hollywood Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m&lt;/a&gt;; #Hollywood; With 109 LAFD Firefighters currently assigned, assisted by neighboring Los Angeles County Firefighters in Automatic Aid, this now hour-long offensive firefight has escalated to Major Emergency status. The fire initially reported as a pair of vehicles burning in a carport, has extended to involve two of three nearly identical side-by-side apartment buildings, including the thirty-two unit, 18,900 square foot two-story apartment building of fire origin - where flames , which had extended to the large common attic on LAFD arrival, caused severe damage to the attic and second floor, including structural compromise and partial collapse. Flames from that building extended to stubbornly involve the attic of one of the nearly identical adjoining apartment buildings, which continues to burn. The woman earlier rescued by first arriving LAFD personnel, and described as being in fair condition with unspecified injuries, has been taken to an area hospital. No other injuries have been confirmed.; FS 41; Batt 5; West Bureau; Council District 13; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC18  BC5  CE83  CM20  CM22  CM52  E11  E203  E220  E226  E227  E229  E235  E261  E27  E278  E29  E3  E41  E61  E88  E97  EA1  EM11  EM14  EM9  HR3  PH1  RA41  RA52  RA76  RA82  RA97  SQ21  T20  T26  T27  T29  T3  T35  T61  T78  UR3  UR88 + LACoFD  BC1 E7  LF8; CH9; 12  13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Major Emergency Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>West</category>
                            <category>#Hollywood</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 18:40</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">Update Greater Alarm Structure Fire 07/12/2023 INC#1353</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#1353; 06:00PM; 7764 W Hollywood Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m&lt;/a&gt;; #Hollywood; With 88 LAFD Firefighters assigned in offensive firefighting operations, assisted by Los Angeles County Firefighters responding in Automatic Aid, this fire has escalated to Greater Alarm status. Firefighters are working to contain the flames to the thirty-two unit, 18,900 square foot two-story apartment building of fire origin, which has experienced structural compromise from the intense flames. The woman earlier rescued by first arriving LAFD personnel, and described as being in fair condition with unspecified injuries, continues to be medically assessed at scene. ; FS 41; Batt 5; West Bureau; Council District 13; BC1  BC11  BC18  BC5  CE83  CM20  CM22  CM52  E203  E220  E226  E227  E235  E261  E27  E29  E3  E41  E61  E97  EA1  EM11  EM14  EM9  HR3  RA41  RA52  RA76  RA82  RA97  T20  T26  T27  T3  T35  T61  UR3  UR88 + LACoFD; CH9; 12  13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>West</category>
                            <category>#Hollywood</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 18:04</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/greater-alarm-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">Greater Alarm Structure Fire 07/12/2023 INC#1353</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/greater-alarm-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#1353; 05:21PM; 7764 W Hollywood Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3pCoi9m&lt;/a&gt;; #Hollywood; PRELIM: Initial report of two vehicles ablaze in the carport of a two-story garden style apartment building, with fire having extended into and fully involved the structure's attic on LAFD arrival. Firefighters have discovered and are rescuing one female civilian (undetermined injuries) from the second floor. An offensive firefight continues. ; FS 41; Batt 5; West Bureau; Council District 13; BC1  BC11  BC18  BC5  CM20  CM22  CM52  E203  E227  E235  E261  E27  E29  E3  E41  E61  E97  EM11  EM14  HR3  RA76  RA803  RA82  RA97  T27  T3  T35  T61  UR3  UR88  + LACoFD; CH9; 12 13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>West</category>
                            <category>#Hollywood</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/greater-alarm-structure-fire-07122023-inc1353" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 17:41</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/contained-grass-fire-07122023-inc0898" hreflang="en">Contained -  Grass Fire 07/12/2023 INC#0898</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/contained-grass-fire-07122023-inc0898" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Contained -  Grass Fire; INC#0898; 01:59PM; 12350 W Van Nuys Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3JRYnBe" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3JRYnBe&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; LAFD crews took little more than an hour to access, confine and full extinguish nearly three acres of vegetation burning between the Foothill Freeway and a flood control channel. No injury. No structures. The fire's cause is suspicious. LAFD Investigators are at the scene.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; AR17  AR25  BC14  BC15  CE83  CM42  DT2  DZ45  E24  E260  E298  E75  E81  E90  E98  FR91  H2  H4  HA2  HA4  HE1  RA7  T60  T98  WT77; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Grass Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/contained-grass-fire-07122023-inc0898" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 14:11</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/grass-fire-07122023-inc0898" hreflang="en">Grass Fire 07/12/2023 INC#0898</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/grass-fire-07122023-inc0898" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Grass Fire; INC#0898; 12:53PM; 12350 W Van Nuys Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3JRYnBe" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3JRYnBe&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; PRELIM: LAFD ground and air response to a grass fire near the Foothill Freeway.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; BC14  BC15  CM42  DT2  DZ45  E24  E260  E298  E75  E81  E98  FR91  T60  T98  WT77; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Grass Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#Pacoima</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/grass-fire-07122023-inc0898" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 13:16</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/brush-fire-automatic-aid-07122023-inc0866" hreflang="en">Brush Fire - Automatic Aid 07/12/2023 INC#0866</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/brush-fire-automatic-aid-07122023-inc0866" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Brush Fire - Automatic Aid; INC#0866; 12:37PM; 3327 Clifden Lane; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/43psvLp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/43psvLp&lt;/a&gt;; #Burbank; PRELIM: LAFD ground and air response in Automatic Aid to assist the Burbank Fire Department at a wildfire within the City of Burbank near the City of Los Angeles border. The LAFD is an assisting agency. All public and media information will come from the Burbank Fire Department.; BC12  BC14  CM40  CM42  DT2  DZ45  E24  E260  E289  E290  E474  E60  E7  E89  E90  E98  EM12  H2  H4  H7  HA2  HA4  HA7  RA102  T60  T89  T90  WT77 + Burbank FD; CH5; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Brush Fire - Automatic Aid</category>
                            <category>#Burbank</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/brush-fire-automatic-aid-07122023-inc0866" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 12:59</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/complete-rescue-07122023-inc0709" hreflang="en">Complete -  Rescue 07/12/2023 INC#0709</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/complete-rescue-07122023-inc0709" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Complete -  Rescue; INC#0709; 11:45AM; 1630 N Main St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/44Hnuig" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/44Hnuig&lt;/a&gt;; #Chinatown; An adult male worker at an electric utility yard reportedly fell ten feet from a crane platform ladder to a catwalk below (that is approximately 50' above ground). LAFD Paramedics climbed to his location, to find the man conscious and alert, in good condition without obvious injury. In accordance with workplace safety protocol, he has been placed in a harness and assisted walking across the catwalk to utilize a freight elevator in descending to ground level and further on-site medical evaluation. No other injuries reported. Media Inquiries: LADWP; FS 1; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; BC1  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM22  E1  E201  E205  E227  E27  E3  E44  E5  EM1  EM11  HR3  RA1  RA20  RA27  RA827  T1  T27  T5  UR5  UR88; CH7; 12; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Rescue</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#Chinatown</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/complete-rescue-07122023-inc0709" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 11:45</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/rescue-07122023-inc0709" hreflang="en">Rescue 07/12/2023 INC#0709</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/rescue-07122023-inc0709" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Rescue; INC#0709; 11:16AM; 1630 N Main St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/44Hnuig" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/44Hnuig&lt;/a&gt;; #Chinatown; PRELIM: One person (unknown age / gender/ condition / site affiliation) at an electric utility yard reportedly stranded on a crane catwalk approximately 50' above ground, after sustaining a ten foot fall and an unspecified injury.; FS 1; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; BC1  BC11  BC2  CM20  CM22  E1  E201  E205  E227  E27  E3  E44  E5  EM1  EM11  HR3  RA1  RA20  RA27  RA827  T1  T27  T5  UR5  UR88; CH7; 12; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Rescue</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#Chinatown</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/rescue-07122023-inc0709" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Wednesday, July 12, 2023 - 11:29</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-07112023-inc1628" hreflang="en">Update Greater Alarm Structure Fire 07/11/2023 INC#1628</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-07112023-inc1628" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#1628; 09:50PM; 131 W Av 43; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3pNS4YD" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3pNS4YD&lt;/a&gt;; #HighlandPark; A previously sustained and bandaged injury by the adult female resident initially suspected of having sustained a burn injury, proved not to be related to the fire. She declined further care. Two other persons later came forward with minor complaints following possible smoke exposure, and are being medically assessed by LAFD Paramedics at the scene. No other injuries reported. The fire, largely involving a shed behind the one story home and excessive outdoor storage with minor damage to the nearby residence, remains under active investigation. ; FS 44; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC2  BC5  CM20  CM22  E1  E12  E16  E201  E202  E210  E212  E227  E3  E44  E47  E55  EA1  EM1  EM13  HR3  RA12  RA3  RA803  T1  T10  T12  T2  T27  T9  UR3  UR88; CH7; 13  14; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#HighlandPark</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-07112023-inc1628" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Tuesday, July 11, 2023 - 21:55</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
