<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.lafd.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alerts Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.lafd.org/</link>
    <description>Alerts Feeds -- Los Angeles Fire Department</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml"/>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 21:37:38 -0800</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate>

    <item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc1556" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 02/04/2024 INC#1556</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc1556" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; INC#1556; 08:43PM; 1914 E 97th St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/3iamLbqRbi29n6KC8" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/3iamLbqRbi29n6KC8&lt;/a&gt;; #Watts; Auto fire, which spread to the adjacent one-story home, causing an attic fire. Offensive mode.; FS 65; Batt 13; South Bureau; Council District 15; BC13  BC706  E21  E233  E264  E64  E65  RA65  RA865  T33  T64; CH9; 12; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>South</category>
                            <category>#Watts</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc1556" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 21:02</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/trafficrelated-water-rescue-02042024-inc1229" hreflang="en">Traffic-related Water Rescue 02/04/2024 INC#1229</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/trafficrelated-water-rescue-02042024-inc1229" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Traffic-related Water Rescue; INC#1229; 06:22PM; 19000 W Oxnard St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/LqWqMB2561WZs9h79" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/LqWqMB2561WZs9h79&lt;/a&gt;; #Tarzana; Several vehicles are disabled in 2-3 feet of water at the intersection of Oxnard St and Donna Ave (and flooding extending between Wilbur and Tampa). No reported injuries, and thankfully the vehicle occupants have remained in their vehicles and not risked going out into the deep water with unpredictable terrain and currents below the surface. LAFD Swiftwater Teams are preparing to send a watercraft out to the vehicles to bring the occupants to safety. ROAD CLOSURE: Due to the flooding, Oxnard will be closed between Wilbur and Tampa. This may result in wider impacts to the immediate area for commuters. Please seek alternate routes and do not attempt to cross flooded roadways. ; FS 93; Batt 17; Valley Bureau; Council District 3; E293  SC1  SW88  T93; CH8; 17; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Traffic-related Water Rescue</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#Tarzana</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/trafficrelated-water-rescue-02042024-inc1229" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 18:51</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0803" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire 02/04/2024 INC#0803</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0803" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#0803; 02:15PM; 560 S Vermont Av; #Koreatown; Firefighters responded to a 13-story boarded-up high-rise building with smoke showing from the upper floors. Crews located a large amount of rubbish burning on the first floor. The smoke filled the building all the way up to the top floor, where the smoke found a way out of the sealed high rise building. Firefighters quickly extinguished the rubbish, but will now be performing a complex ventilation operation to evacuate the smoke from all 13 floors. Firefighters found several people inside, who were effectively rescued. Ultimately, it took 78 firefighters 30 minutes to access, confine, and extinguish the flames. No reported injuries. Cause under investigation.; FS 13; Batt 11; Central Bureau; Council District 10; BC1  BC11  BC18  BC706  CM20  CM22  E11  E13  E20  E211  E220  E226  E227  E229  E26  E261  E29  E3  E52  E6  E87  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM14  EM5  HR3  RA11  RA13  RA3  RA52  RA6  RA803  RA811  RA813  SO1  SQ21  SQ87  T11  T20  T26  T27  T29  T61  UR3  UR88; CH7; 13  14  16; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#Koreatown</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0803" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 15:18</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc0803" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 02/04/2024 INC#0803</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc0803" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; INC#0803; 02:15PM; 3190 W 6th St; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/bNaRzJvTQGffxEyc9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/bNaRzJvTQGffxEyc9&lt;/a&gt;; #Koreatown; Approximately 13-story high rise (vacant) with smoke showing from multiple floors. Offensive mode.; FS 13; Batt 11; Central Bureau; Council District 10; BC1  BC11  BC18  BC706  CM20  CM22  E11  E13  E20  E211  E220  E226  E227  E229  E26  E261  E29  E3  E52  E6  E87  EM1  EM11  EM14  EM5  HR3  RA11  RA13  RA3  RA52  RA6  RA803  RA811  RA813  SO1  SQ21  SQ87  T11  T20  T26  T27  T29  T61  UR3  UR88; CH9; 13  14; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#Koreatown</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc0803" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 14:26</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire 02/04/2024 INC#0602</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#0602; 12:33PM; 4404 E Toland Pl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/2QDJZ29PQH923YG39" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/2QDJZ29PQH923YG39&lt;/a&gt;; #EagleRock; Firefighters responded to an *ascending* hillside home that was two stories, plus an attic converted to a living space. Crews made access to the structure, advancing hose lines and achieving roof ventilation, but excessive storage inside fueled a rapidly growing fire, which forced firefighters to retreat into defensive mode (fighting from the exterior only). While the structure was a total loss, firefighters successfully defended the nearby vegetation and adjacent homes. Thankfully, both residents and their canine, who were home at the time of the fire, escaped without harm. They will be displaced and Red Cross is responding to assist them, and LAFD will issue a SAVE card (Supplying Aid to Victims of Emergency) for some financial assistance. Ultimately, it took 74 firefighters 57 min to access, confine, and extinguish the flames. No reported injuries. The cause of the fire is under investigation. 

74 ff 57min; FS 55; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; AR1  BC1  BC14  BC2  BC5  CM20  CM22  E1  E12  E201  E203  E212  E220  E227  E235  E250  E27  E42  E44  E55  E56  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM5  HR3  RA12  RA27  RA55  RA56  RA827  RA850  SO1  SQ21  T1  T12  T20  T27  T3  T35  T50  UR27  UR88; CH7; 12  13  15; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#EagleRock</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 13:01</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">Update Greater Alarm Structure Fire 02/04/2024 INC#0602</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#0602; 12:25PM; 4404 E Toland Pl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/nwwZP4ZyBCvj4aVW8" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/nwwZP4ZyBCvj4aVW8&lt;/a&gt;; #EagleRock; Firefighters continue to battle flames in the two-story hillside home, now in defensive mode. The home contains excessive storage that impedes firefighters' access and provides extra fuel for the fire to burn. Firefighters have been able to keep the fire from spreading to the brush that surrounds the home. ; FS 55; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; BC1  BC14  BC2  BC5  CM20  CM22  E1  E12  E201  E203  E212  E220  E227  E235  E250  E27  E42  E44  E55  E56  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM5  HR3  RA12  RA27  RA55  RA56  RA827  RA850  SO1  SQ21  T1  T12  T20  T27  T3  T35  T50  UR27  UR88; CH9; 12  13  15; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#EagleRock</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 12:29</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-now-out-02042024-inc0575" hreflang="en">Structure Fire - Now Out 02/04/2024 INC#0575</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-now-out-02042024-inc0575" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire - Now Out; INC#0575; 11:19AM; 7142 1/2 S Ramsgate Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/qxR77GYC8v4aQmcB7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/qxR77GYC8v4aQmcB7&lt;/a&gt;; #Westchester; Twenty-eight LAFD firefighters extinguished flames in one unit of a multi-family residential structure in 30 minutes. Crews contained the flames to just one unit. No reported injuries. Cause under investigation.; FS 5; Batt 4; West Bureau; Council District 11; BC18  BC9  E205  E266  E51  E63  E67  RA57  RA866  T5  T66; CH9; 12; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire - Now Out</category>
                            <category>West</category>
                            <category>#Westchester</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-now-out-02042024-inc0575" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 12:01</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">Structure Fire 02/04/2024 INC#0602</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Structure Fire; INC#0602; 11:36AM; 4404 E Toland Pl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/VeGkLpPm2RQjxMr6A" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/VeGkLpPm2RQjxMr6A&lt;/a&gt;; #EagleRock; Two-story descending hillside home with heavy fire showing from the second floor.  Offensive mode.; FS 55; Batt 2; Central Bureau; Council District 1; BC2  BC5  E12  E212  E250  E42  E55  RA55  RA850  T12  T50; CH9; 13; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Central</category>
                            <category>#EagleRock</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/structure-fire-02042024-inc0602" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 11:48</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/evacuation-order-02042024" hreflang="en">EVACUATION ORDER 02/04/2024</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/evacuation-order-02042024" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>EVACUATION ORDER; 09:15AM; MAP: &lt;a href="https://lafd.maps.arcgis.com/apps/Media/index.html?appid=ba8cfed4b4a04d49b7489eb8300727a8" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://lafd.maps.arcgis.com/apps/Media/index.html?appid=ba8cfed4b4a04d49b7489eb8300727a8&lt;/a&gt;; #ShadowHills; EVACUATE NOW due to the high risk of debris flow triggered by heavy rain from the storm impacting the area today through Tuesday. The EVACUATION ORDER is for the La Tuna Canyon Road area, with borders of Horse Haven Street to the North, Martindale Avenue to the East, Penrose Street to the South, Ledge Avenue to the West. Evacuation Centers for people and household pets have opened at Sunland Senior Citizen Center (8640 Fenwick St, Sunland, CA 91040) and Lake View Terrace Recreation Center (11075 Foothill Blvd, Lake View Terrace, CA 91342). Large animals can be evacuated to Hansen Dam Horse Park (11127 Orcas Ave. Lake View Terrace, CA 91342) and the LA Equestrian Center (480 Riverside Dr, Burbank, CA 91506). Check lafd.org/alerts for updates on this evacuation order. Debris flows can bring water, mud, boulders, and other debris that can cover cars and houses.  Pack all people and pets into your vehicle and leave the area immediately. More information, including a map, can be found at www.lafd.org/news

EVACUEN AHORA debido al flujo de escombros de alto riesgo provocado por las fuertes lluvias de la tormenta que impactaran el área desde hoy hasta el martes. La ORDEN DE EVACUACIÓN es para el área La Tuna Canyon Road, con límites de Horse Haven St. al norte, Martindale Ave. al este, Penrose St al sur, Ledge Ave al oeste. Se han abierto refugios para personas y mascotas domésticas en Sunland Senior Citizen Center (8640 Fenwick St, Sunland, CA 91040) y Lake View Terrace Recreation Center (11075 Foothill Blvd, Lake View Terrace, CA 91342). Los animales grandes pueden ser evacuados al Hansen Dam Horse Park (11127 Orcas Ave. Lake View Terrace, CA 91342) y al LA Equestrian Center (480 Riverside Dr, Burbank, CA 91506). Visite lafd.org/alerts para obtener actualizaciones sobre esta orden de evacuación.
Los flujos de escombros pueden traer agua, lodo, rocas y otros escombros que pueden cubrir automóviles y casas. Empaque a todas las personas y mascotas en su vehículo y abandone el área inmediatamente. Puede encontrar más información, incluido un mapa, en www.lafd.org/news; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>EVACUATION ORDER</category>
                            <category>#ShadowHills</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/evacuation-order-02042024" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 09:16</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire 02/03/2024 INC#1609</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>KNOCKDOWN Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#1609; 11:51PM; 7255 N Clybourn Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/ayaoto8T2gajhhQu9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://maps.app.goo.gl/ayaoto8T2gajhhQu9&lt;/a&gt;; #SunValley; It took 78 firefighters 61 minutes operating in defensive mode to extinguish the blaze consuming the 80' x 120' one-story commercial structure. One man from the scene was transported to a local hospital with a medical complaint (not directly related to smoke or fire). LAFD Heavy Equipment and RS3 (remote firefighting vehicle) will be performing an extended operation to ensure all the hot spots and smoldering debris are uncovered for extinguishment. No firefighter injuries. Cause under investigation.; FS 89; Batt 14; Valley Bureau; Council District 2; AR1  BC11  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E102  E227  E239  E260  E27  E278  E289  E298  E60  E75  E77  E86  E87  E89  EA1  EM14  EM5  HE1  HR3  PI3  RA77  RA86  RA889  RA89  RS3  SO1  SQ87  T27  T39  T60  T78  T89  T98  UR27  UR88; CH8; 12  13  15; Nicholas Prange</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
                            <category>Valley</category>
                            <category>#SunValley</category>
                            <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-greater-alarm-structure-fire-02032024-inc1609" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
                            <pubDate>Sunday, February 4, 2024 - 00:31</pubDate>
                            <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
                            </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
