<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.lafd.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alerts Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.lafd.org/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml"/>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 21:45:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Wednesday, March 8, 2023 - 06:49</pubDate>

    <item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148-1" hreflang="en">Update Major Emergency Structure Fire #AdamsFire 03/08/2023 INC#0148</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148-1" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update #AdamsFire Major Emergency Structure Fire; INC#0148; 06:30AM; 2615 S Grand Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK&lt;/a&gt;; #HistoricSouthCentral; Two LAFD Firefighters have been *treated at the scene* for respiratory complaints following smoke inhalation during the fierce firefight. No civilian injuries have been reported. LAFD Firefighters will remain at the location this morning to further salvage building contents, assist County of Los Angeles officials and support the still active LAFD investigation into the cause of the fire. LAFD Public Information Officer Captain Jacob Raabe remains at scene to assist the media.; FS 10; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 9; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC13  BC18  BC5  CM20  CM21  CM22  E10  E13  E14  E15  E201  E203  E205  E209  E210  E211  E215  E220  E221  E226  E227  E229  E248  E3  E4  E46  E85  E9  EA1  EA2  EM1  EM11  EM13  EM18  HR3  PI5  RA10  RA14  RA15  RA3  RA46  RA803  RM1  RM3  SQ21  T1  T10  T11  T15  T20  T21  T26  T27  T29  T3  T48  T5  T9  UR3  UR88; CH7; 13; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Major Emergency Structure Fire</category>
          <category>Central</category>
          <category>#HistoricSouthCentral</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148-1" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Wednesday, March 8, 2023 - 06:49</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148-0" hreflang="en">Update Major Emergency Structure Fire #AdamsFire 03/08/2023 INC#0148</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148-0" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update #AdamsFire Major Emergency Structure Fire; INC#0148; 05:30AM; 2615 S Grand Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK&lt;/a&gt;; #HistoricSouthCentral; One LAFD Firefighter is now being treated by LAFD Paramedics for smoke inhalation sustained during the fierce firefight in a government office building that is reported to house several County of Los Angeles agencies. LAFD Public Information Officer Captain Jacob Raabe is on scene. Media Staging is at the intersection of Adams Blvd and Hill Street. The fire cause remains under active investigation.; FS 10; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 9; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC13  BC18  BC5  CM20  CM21  CM22  E10  E13  E14  E15  E201  E203  E205  E209  E210  E211  E215  E220  E221  E226  E227  E229  E248  E3  E4  E46  E85  E9  EA1  EA2  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  PI5  RA10  RA14  RA15  RA3  RA803  RM1  RM3  SQ21  T1  T10  T11  T15  T20  T21  T26  T27  T29  T3  T48  T5  T9  UR3  UR88; CH9; 13  14; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Major Emergency Structure Fire</category>
          <category>Central</category>
          <category>#HistoricSouthCentral</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148-0" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Wednesday, March 8, 2023 - 05:37</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/knockdown-adamsfire-major-emergency-structure-fire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">Knockdown - #AdamsFire Major Emergency Structure Fire 03/08/2023 INC#0148</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/knockdown-adamsfire-major-emergency-structure-fire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Knockdown - #AdamsFire Major Emergency Structure Fire; INC#0148; 04:57AM; 2615 S Grand Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK&lt;/a&gt;; #HistoricSouthCentral; It took 160 LAFD Firefighters less than one hour to access, confine and extinguish heavy fire throughout the top floor of a six-story office building owned by the County of Los Angeles, and housing administrative offices for several County agencies. No injuries reported. LAFD Public Information Officer Captain Jacob Raabe is on scene to assist the media. The fire cause remains under active investigation.; FS 10; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 9; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC13  BC18  BC5  CM20  CM21  CM22  E10  E13  E14  E15  E201  E203  E205  E209  E210  E211  E215  E220  E221  E226  E227  E229  E248  E3  E4  E46  E85  E9  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  RA10  RA14  RA15  RA3  RA803  PI5  RM1  RM3  SQ21  T1  T10  T11  T15  T20  T21  T26  T27  T29  T3  T48  T5  T9  UR3  UR88 ; CH9; 13  14; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Major Emergency Structure Fire</category>
          <category>Central</category>
          <category>#HistoricSouthCentral</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/knockdown-adamsfire-major-emergency-structure-fire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Wednesday, March 8, 2023 - 05:11</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">Update Major Emergency Structure Fire #AdamsFire 03/08/2023 INC#0148</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update #AdamsFire Major Emergency Structure Fire; INC#0148; 04:50AM; 2615 S Grand Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK&lt;/a&gt;; #HistoricSouthCentral; With 160 LAFD Firefighters assigned, this active firefight in a six-story office building is categorized as a Major Emergency incident, and formally known as the Adams Fire. The pre-1960 concrete structure is owned by the County of Los Angeles, and houses administrative offices for several County agencies. LAFD Public Information Officer Captain Jacob Raabe is en route, ETA 5:00 AM. Significant progress is being made, as the offensive firefight continues with no injuries reported.; FS 10; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 9; AR1  BC1  BC11  BC13  BC18  BC5  CM20  CM21  CM22  E10  E13  E14  E15  E201  E203  E209  E210  E211  E215  E220  E221  E226  E227  E229  E3  E4  E46  E85  E9  EA1  EM1  EM11  EM13  HR3  PI5  RA10  RA14  RA15  RA3  RA803  SQ21  T1  T10  T11  T15  T20  T21  T26  T27  T29  T3  T9  UR3  UR88 ; CH9; 13  14; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Major Emergency Structure Fire</category>
          <category>Central</category>
          <category>#HistoricSouthCentral</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-major-emergency-structure-fire-adamsfire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Wednesday, March 8, 2023 - 04:54</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/greater-alarm-structure-fire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">Greater Alarm Structure Fire 03/08/2023 INC#0148</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/greater-alarm-structure-fire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Greater Alarm Structure Fire; INC#0148; 03:58AM; 2615 S Grand Av; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3ITRWMK&lt;/a&gt;; #HistoricSouthCentral; PRELIM: 6 Story Office Building With Heavy Fire Showing From 6th Floor.; FS 10; Batt 1; Central Bureau; Council District 9; BC1  BC11  BC13  BC18  BC5  CM20  CM22  E10  E14  E15  E209  E210  E211  E215  E226  E227  E3  E4  E9  EA2  EM11  HR3  RA10  RA3  RA803  SQ21  T10  T11  T15  T26  T27  T9  UR3  UR88; CH9; 13  14; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>Greater Alarm Structure Fire</category>
          <category>Central</category>
          <category>#HistoricSouthCentral</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/greater-alarm-structure-fire-03082023-inc0148" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Wednesday, March 8, 2023 - 04:13</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569-1" hreflang="en">Update River Rescue 03/07/2023 INC#0569</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569-1" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update River Rescue; INC#0569; 12:00PM; 10798 N Laurel Canyon Bl; #Pacoima; The one and only victim is now described as a homeless 23 year-old male, who fell into the swift moving water (18" deep / 8-10 mph) of the concrete lined and fenced Pacoima Wash flood control channel near Foothill Boulevard, a distance of 2.5 miles from where he was rescued. He was transported to an area hospital in fair condition for treatment of hypothermia and abrasions to his hands.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; AO1  AO2  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E226  E260  E275  E278  E289  E298  E35  E75  E76  E81  E86  E88  E89  E98  EM14  H3  H4  HA3  HA4  HR3  RA18  RA60  RA76  SW88  T26  T60  T75  T78  T89  T98  UR88; CH8; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>River Rescue</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#Pacoima</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569-1" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Tuesday, March 7, 2023 - 12:07</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/complete-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">COMPLETE -  River Rescue 03/07/2023 INC#0569</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/complete-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>COMPLETE -  River Rescue; INC#0569; 11:21AM; 10798 N Laurel Canyon Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3Ys1UKY" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3Ys1UKY&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; The one and only known victim has been safely rescued from within a tunnel that allows the Pacoima Wash flood control channel to cross beneath surface streets and the Golden State (I-5) Freeway. The successful rescue of the young adult male was performed by an LAFD Swift Water Rescue team member using a tethered inflatable LAFD Swift Water Rescue boat. At the time of the rescue the storm water runoff within the concrete lined channel was approximately 18" deep and moving at 8-10 miles per hour. The victim is being medically examined for hypothermic symptoms, and will be transported to an area hospital. NOTE: This incident underscores the life threatening danger of storm water runoff that can linger long after the rain has passed. We're grateful for the witnesses who promptly called 9-1-1, and did not attempt to perform a spontaneous rescue, which could have led to multiple victims and the loss of lives. Though our skies are now clear, storm drains and flood control channels remain life threatening, and we ask parents to make sure all household members are aware of the danger. When it comes to fast moving floodwater, even that which is a few inches deep, the LAFD says 'Stay Away and Stay Alive'.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; AO1  AO2  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E226  E260  E275  E278  E289  E298  E35  E75  E76  E81  E86  E88  E89  E98  EM14  H3  H4  HA3  HA4  HR3  RA18  RA60  RA76  SW88  T26  T60  T75  T78  T89  T98  UR88; CH5; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>River Rescue</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#Pacoima</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/complete-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Tuesday, March 7, 2023 - 11:32</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569-0" hreflang="en">Update River Rescue 03/07/2023 INC#0569</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569-0" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update River Rescue; INC#0569; 10:45AM; 10798 N Laurel Canyon Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3Ys1UKY" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3Ys1UKY&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; With the young adult male victim now determined to be well within a tunnel that allows the Pacoima Wash flood control channel to cross beneath the Golden State (I-5) Freeway, the rescue plan has transitioned to LAFD Swift Water Rescue and LAFD Urban Search and Rescue personnel using a tethered inflatable LAFD Swift Water Rescue boat to perform the rescue. The storm water runoff with the concrete lined channel remains 18" deep, moving at 8-10 miles per hour.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District 7; AO1  AO2  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E226  E260  E278  E289  E298  E35  E76  E81  E86  E88  E89  E98  EM14  H3  H4  HA3  HA4  HR3  RA18  RA60  RA76  SW88  T26  T60  T78  T89  T98  UR88; CH5; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>River Rescue</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#Pacoima</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569-0" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Tuesday, March 7, 2023 - 10:56</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">Update River Rescue 03/07/2023 INC#0569</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>Update River Rescue; INC#0569; 10:30AM; 10700 Laurel Canyon Bl; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3Ys1UKY" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3Ys1UKY&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; LAFD crews have discovered the (teenage?) male in distress, now clinging to a concrete divider within the Pacoima Wash flood control channel near Laurel Canyon Boulevard. The concrete lined channel appears to contain 18" of storm water runoff moving at *5-8 mph*. LAFD ground crews will soon commence rope rescue of the victim.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; AO1  AO2  BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E226  E260  E278  E289  E298  E35  E76  E81  E86  E88  E89  E98  EM14  H3  H4  HA3  HA4  HR3  RA18  RA60  RA76  SW88  T26  T60  T78  T89  T98  UR88; CH5; 17; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>River Rescue</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#Pacoima</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/update-river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Tuesday, March 7, 2023 - 10:36</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>
<item>
  <title><a href="/alert/river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">River Rescue 03/07/2023 INC#0569</a></title>
  <link><a href="/alert/river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">view</a></link>
  <description>River Rescue; INC#0569; 10:06AM; 10999 Haddon Ave; MAP: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/3myWErT" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://bit.ly/3myWErT&lt;/a&gt;; #Pacoima; PRELIM: Widespread LAFD ground and air response upon several 911 callers reporting a teenage male in distress, within the Pacoima Wash flood control channel, which appears to contain as many as 18" of storm water runoff moving at 5-8 mph. Last civilian sighting of person in distress was at 10:21 AM at Haddon Avenue and Pacoima Wash.; FS 98; Batt 12; Valley Bureau; Council District City of San Fernando; BC12  BC14  BC5  CM40  CM42  E226  E260  E278  E289  E298  E35  E76  E81  E86  E89  E98  EM14  H3  H4  HA3  HA4  HR3  RA60  RA76  T26  T60  T78  T89  T98  UR88; CH5; Brian Humphrey</description>
  <category>River Rescue</category>
          <category>Valley</category>
          <category>#Pacoima</category>
          <guid isPermaLink="false"><a href="/alert/river-rescue-03072023-inc0569" hreflang="en">view</a></guid>
          <pubDate>Tuesday, March 7, 2023 - 10:26</pubDate>
          <source url="https://www.lafd.org/alerts-rss.xml">Alerts Feed</source>
          </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
